Guide to the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1985-2010; Accession 2014-A-075
  - Records of Dean Gus Speth
    - Faculty Meeting - Mar 6, 2002, 2002 March (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Meeting - Mar 27, 2002, 2002 March (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Meeting - Apr 24, 2002, 2002 April (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Meeting - May 7, 2002, 2002 May (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Meeting - May 22, 2002, 2002 May (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Meeting - Sep 11, 2002, 2002 September (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Special Faculty Meeting -Sep 25, 2002, 2002 September (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Meeting - Oct 23, 2002, 2002 October (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Special Faculty Meeting - Oct 30, 2002, 2002 October (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Meeting - Nov 20, 2002, 2002 November (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Meeting - Dec 18, 2002, 2002 December (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Meeting - Jan 15, 2003, 2003 January (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Special Faculty Meeting - Jan 29, 2003, 2003 January (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Meeting - Feb 12, 2003, 2003 February (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Special Faculty Meeting - Feb 26, 2003, 2003 February (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Meeting - Mar 26, 2003, 2003 March (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Special Faculty Meeting - Apr 2, 2003, 2003 April (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Meeting - Apr 16, 2003, 2003 April (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Meeting - May 14, 2003, 2003 May (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Meeting - Sep 17, 2003, 2003 September (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Faculty Meeting - Oct 15, 2003, 2003 October (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Meeting - Nov 12, 2003, 2003 November (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Meeting - Dec 17, 2003, 2003 December (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Faculty Meeting - Jan 21, 2003, 2003 January (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Faculty Meeting - Feb 18, 2004, 2004 February (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Faculty Meeting - Apr 21, 2004, 2004 April (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Faculty Meeting - May 19, 2004, 2004 May (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Faculty Meeting - Sep 17, 2004, 2004 September (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Faculty Meeting - Dec 16, 2004, 2004 December (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Faculty Meeting - Feb 4, 2005, 2005 February (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Faculty Meeting - Mar 4, 2005, 2005 March (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Faculty Meeting - Apr 22, 2005, 2005 April (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Faculty Meeting - May 20, 2005, 2005 May (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Faculty Meeting - Sep 16, 2005, 2005 September (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Faculty Meeting - Nov 11, 2005, 2005 November (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Faculty Meeting - Dec 9, 2005, 2005 December (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Faculty Meeting - Feb 24, 2006, 2006 February (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Faculty Meeting - Oct 20 2006, 2006 October (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Meeting Agenda - Jan 26, 2007, 2007 January (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Meeting - Mar 2, 2007, 2007 March (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - FES Faculty Meeting - Apr 13, 2007, 2007 April (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Meeting - Sep 14, 2007, 2007 September (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Meeting Agenda - Oct 26, 2007, 2007 October (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Meeting - Dec 14, 2007, 2007 December (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Meeting - Jan 25, 2008, 2008 February (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Meeting - Feb 22, 2008, 2008 February (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Meeting - April 18, 2008, 2008 April (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Meeting - May 16, 2008, 2008 May (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Meeting - Sep 12, 2008, 2008 September (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Meeting - Nov 14, 2008, 2008 November (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - FES Faculty Meeting - Feb 6, 2009, 2009 February (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - FES Faculty Meeting - Mar 6, 2009, 2009 March (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - FES Faculty Meeting - May 15, 2009, 2009 May (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - FES Faculty/Senior Staff Meeting - Oct 2, 2009, 2009 October (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - FES Ladder Faculty Meeting - Oct 2, 2009, 2009 October (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - FES Faculty/Senior Staff Meeting - Nov 13, 2009, 2009 November (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - FES Ladder Faculty Meeting - Nov 13, 2009, 2009 November 13 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - FES Faculty-Senior Staff Meeting - Dec 11, 2009, 2009 December (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - FES Ladder Faculty Meeting - Dec 11, 2009, 2009 December (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - FES Faculty-Senior Staff Meeting - Jan 18, 2010, 2010 January (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - FES Ladder Faculty Meeting - Jan 18, 2010, 2010 January (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - FES Faculty-Senior Staff Meeting - Feb 26, 2010, 2010 February (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Society of American Foresters reports
    - Society of American Foresters (SAF) Interim Status Report Table of Contents Standard I - VIII, 1999 July (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - SAF Interim Status Report Appendices A-F, 1999 July (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - SAF Interim Status Report Appendices G-M, 1999 July (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - SAF Accreditation Report for MF Degree: Table of Contents and Standards I - VIII, 2003 October (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - SAF Accreditation Report for MF Degree Volume II: Appendices I.1 - I.4, 2003 October (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - SAF Accreditation Report for MF Degree Volume II: Appendices I.5 - II.3, 2003 October (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - SAF Accreditation Report for MF Degree Appendix II.4, 2003 October (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - SAF Accreditation Report for MF Degree Appendices II.5 - IV.1, 2003 October (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - SAF Accreditation Report for MF Degree Appendices IV.2 - V.2, 2003 October (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - SAF Accreditation Report for MF Degree Appendices V.3 - VIII.1, 2003 October (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Society of American Foresters - Status Report, 2003 October (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Society of American Foresters Accreditation, 2000 November - 2001 February (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Society of American Foresters Committee on Accreditation, 2008 January (Box 21, Folder 10)